<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nirjhar Barma on deBlog</title>
    <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/authors/nirjhar-barma/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nirjhar Barma on deBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 12:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://debloga.vercel.app/authors/nirjhar-barma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hiding exe with Image extension</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 12:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/picture/</guid>
      <description>Hiding exe with Image extension What we always see is not what it is- A file could look innocent but it could hide the most dangerous malware. Windows hides file extensions by default, therefore there is an infinite possible ways to send a malware unnoticed, two way of doing it is hiding/attaching it with an image-
This blog is only for educational purpose and in no way intended for malicious purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFID-Radio Frequency Identification</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/rfid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:20:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/rfid/</guid>
      <description>RFID (RADIO FREQUENCY INDENTIFICATION)
Radio Frequency Identification (RFID) refers to a wireless system comprised of two components: tags and readers. The reader is a device that has one or more antennas that emit radio waves and receive signals back from the RFID tag. Tags, which use radio waves to communicate their identity and other information to nearby readers, can be passive or active. Passive RFID tags are powered by the reader and do not have a battery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL MEDIA: THE SURFACE DARK WEB</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/nirjhar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/nirjhar/</guid>
      <description>SOCIAL MEDIA: THE SURFACE DARK WEB
In recent years, the social media has become the common hunting grounds for all hackers/criminals which can affect to a national level or just to seek revenge to an individual. Pentagon officials are increasingly worried that state-backed hackers/criminals are using social media platforms such as Twitter and Facebook to break into computer networks of high ranked or individuals. Therefore exercising such power comes at a high stake.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
