<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rishi Paul on deBlog</title>
    <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/authors/rishi-paul/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rishi Paul on deBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://debloga.vercel.app/authors/rishi-paul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>C Demystified: Mastering Programming</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/learnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/learnc/</guid>
      <description>Discover one of the earliest programming languages and what it has to offer What is C?
Why do I need to learn about the 3rd letter of the alphabet!? Is something that you’re probably thinking about right now.
C is a low-level language.
It didn’t use to be. Back in the day when people carved punch cards out of granite, C was an incredible way to be free of the drudgery of lower-level languages like assembly19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet deBlog</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:55:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to deBlog! Built with HUGO, The world’s fastest framework for building websites.
Features of deBlog Extremely fast
Uses minimal bandwith
Great SEO SEO improvement Use SVG and Webp instead of JPGs, PNGS etc. Use proper metadata Use Linkable assets Target Brand New Keywords How can I contribute? If you wish to add your own article or make changes in order to improve this site, head to the &amp;ldquo;deBlog repository&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://debloga.vercel.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://debloga.vercel.app/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hello there! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m Rishi, a passionate frontend developer with a keen eye for creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces. My journey in the realm of web development has been an exciting adventure, marked by the continuous pursuit of excellence in crafting seamless digital experiences.
While my expertise lies in frontend technologies, I am fueled by a curiosity that extends beyond the boundaries of the browser. Eager to delve into the realms of Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, and Data Science, I am on a mission to expand my skill set and embrace the future of technology.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
